Ernst Bacon Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1898-1990 (Box 41-51)
  - General Correspondence (Box 43-51)
    General correspondence, contains other letters not listed in Family correspondence or letters to the editor. It contains letters from fans, students, friends, and professional acquaintances.
    - 506th Army Air Forces Band, 1944-45 (Box-folder 43/1)
    - Adams, Ansel, 1951-80, n.d. (Box-folder 43/2)
    - Adams, Marion, n.d. (Box-folder 43/3)
    - Adams, Virgina, n.d. (Box-folder 43/4)
    - Adler, Kurt, 1983 May 26 (Box-folder 43/5)
    - Aid To Music Program, 1961 (Box-folder 43/6)
    - Alkahest Celebrity Bureau, 1938 Sept. 21 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - All Souls Parish, 1973 Feb. 20 (Box-folder 43/8)
    - Allen, William Duncan, 1983 May 26 (Box-folder 43/9)
    - Alpha Mu Music Honor Society, n.d. (Box-folder 43/10)
    - Ameling, Elly, 1979 (Box-folder 43/11)
    - American Conservatory of Music see: Sowerby, Leo
    - American Conservatory Theatre, 1977 Jan. 21 (Box-folder 43/12)
    - The American Mercury, 1947 (Box-folder 43/13)
    - American Music Center, 1958 Jan. 29 (Box-folder 43/14)
    - The American Music Teacher, 1966, 1973-76 (Box-folder 43/15)
    - American Opera Company, 1948 May 24 (Box-folder 43/16)
    - American Shakespeare Festival see: Langner, Lawrence
    - The American Scholar,1966, 1974, n.d. (Box-folder 43/17)
    - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers, 1974, 1976, 1987, 1989 (Box-folder 43/18)
    - Amherst College, 1931, 1989 (Box-folder 43/19)
    - Arizona State University, 1974, Also contains music written in honor of Ernst Bacon by Johnson, David N. (Box-folder 43/20)
    - Arts Club of Washington, 1948 (Box-folder 43/21)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1938-47 (Box-folder 43/22)
    - ASCAP see: American Society of Composers, Authors and Publisher
    - Associated Music Publishers, Inc., 1943-48 (Box-folder 43/23)
    - The Atheneum Arts Foundation, 1966 (Box-folder 43/24)
    - Atheneum Publishers, 1964-65 (Box-folder 43/25)
    - The Atlantic Monthly, 1965-69, n.d. see also: New Republic (Box-folder 43/26)
    - "A" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 43/27)
    - Bales, Dorothy, 1979-81, n.d. (Box-folder 43/28)
    - The Baldwin Piano Company, 1931-44 (Box-folder 43/29)
    - Balogh, Ernö, n.d. (Box-folder 43/30)
    - The Bank of California, 1979 July 25 (Box-folder 43/31)
    - Bard College, 1938 (Box-folder 43/32)
    - Barlow, Wayne see: The University of Rochester
    - Barr, Stringfellow, 1971 May 21 (Box-folder 43/33)
    - Bauer, Harold see: The Baldwin Piano Company
    - Baylor University, 1966-67 (Box-folder 43/34)
    - Beach, Victoria Gorcoff, 1975-84, n.d. (Box-folder 43/35)
    - Behrend, Jeanne, 1943-1947, 1961, 1976, 1981 (Box-folder 43/36)
    - Bennington College see: Luening, Otto see: Nowak, Lionel
    - Berkeley Daily Gazette, 1965 Sept. 22 see also: The Independent (Box-folder 43/37)
    - Bernat, Juliette see: Lombard, Eugene and Juliette
    - Bernstein, Leonard see: New York Philharmonic
    - Bialosky, Marshall, 1984 (Box-folder 43/38)
    - Biographical Encyclopedia of the World, 1946 Dec. 9 (Box-folder 43/39)
    - Black Mountain College, 1940-44 see also: Sly, Alan (Box-folder 43/40)
    - Bloch, Ernest, 1933-36 (Box-folder 43/41)
    - Boatwright, Helen, 1964, 1972-79, 1983-89, n.d. and Howard Boatwright (Box-folder 43/42)
    - Boosey & Hawkes, Inc., 1948, 1975 (Box-folder 43/43)
    - The Boston Globe, 1958 June 3 (Box-folder 43/44)
    - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1966, 1975 (Box-folder 43/45)
    - Boston University, n.d. (Box-folder 43/46)
    - Branch Banking & Trust Company, 1940 Dec. 23 (Box-folder 43/47)
    - Bricken, Carl, 1937 Aug. 17 see also: University of Chicago see also: University of Wisconsin (Box-folder 43/48)
    - British Broadcasting Corpration, 1972 Dec. 22 (Box-folder 43/49)
    - Broude Brothers, 1974 Apr. 1 (Box-folder 43/50)
    - Brunswick, Mark and Ruth see: Placement Committee for German and Austrian Musicians
    - Bufano, Remo, 1933 May 8 (Box-folder 43/51)
    - Bureau of Fine Arts, 1917 (Box-folder 43/52)
    - Butterworth, Neil, 1975 Jan. 24 (Box-folder 43/53)
    - Bynner, Witter, 1928 Jan. 3 (Box-folder 43/54)
    - "B" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 43/55)
    - California State University, 1987, n.d. (Box-folder 43/56)
    - Callaway, Paul, 1974 May 27 (Box-folder 43/57)
    - Cambridge Records, Inc., 1964 (Box-folder 43/58)
    - Camp Minocqua, 1917 (Box-folder 43/59)
    - Campolindo High School, 1976 July 20 (Box-folder 43/60)
    - Carl Fischer Inc., 1938-39 (Box-folder 43/61)
    - Carleton College, 1981 Feb. 20 (Box-folder 43/62)
    - Carmel Bach Festival, 1977 Aug. 15 (Box-folder 43/63)
    - Carmel Music Society, 1976 Dec. 17 (Box-folder 43/64)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1947 (Box-folder 43/65)
    - Carus, Helena, 1926-27, 1940, 1950, 1965, n.d. (Box-folder 43/66)
    - The Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine, 1960-63 (Box-folder 43/67)
    - The Catholic University of America, 1966 Dec. 28 (Box-folder 43/68)
    - Cazenovia Junior College, 1957 (Box-folder 43/69)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1964 (Box-folder 43/70)
    - Central City Oprea House Association see: University of Denver
    - Charlotte Symphony Orchestra Society, 1946 May 30 (Box-folder 43/71)
    - Chasins, Abram, 1962, 1981 see also: The New York Times (Box-folder 43/72)
    - The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1946 Aug. 20 (Box-folder 43/73)
    - Chicago Daily News, n.d. (Box-folder 43/74)
    - Chicago Little Symphony see: Johnson, Thor
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1984-85 (Box-folder 43/75)
    - Cieciora, Phillip J., 1981 (Box-folder 43/76)
    - Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra, 1931-47 (Box-folder 43/77)
    - Cincinnati Zoo Opera Company, 1926 May 11 (Box-folder 43/78)
    - Circle Blueprint Company, Inc., 1938, 1943 (Box-folder 43/79)
    - Circle in the Square, 1975 Dec. 18 (Box-folder 43/80)
    - Citkowitz, Israel, n.d. (Box-folder 43/81)
    - The City College of the University of New York, 1966 Jan. 20 see also: Jahoda, Fritz (Box-folder 43/82)
    - Civic Concert Service, Inc., 1939 Dec. 11 (Box-folder 43/83)
    - The Civic Symphony Society, 1943 (Box-folder 43/84)
    - The Clark-Brewer Teachers Agency, 1937-44 (Box-folder 43/85)
    - Clark Music Co., 1945, 1948 (Box-folder 43/86)
    - Clavier, 1981-85, n.d. (Box-folder 43/87)
    - The Cleveland Museum of Art, 1960-69 (Box-folder 43/88)
    - Clifton, Chalmers, 1942-44 (Box-folder 43/89)
    - Coates, Helen G. see: New York Philharmonic
    - The College of William and Mary, 1939 (Box-folder 43/90)
    - The College Young Men's Christian Association of Northwestern University, 1917 Mar. 6 (Box-folder 43/91)
    - Colorado Women's College, 1967 Feb. 28 (Box-folder 43/92)
    - Columbia Artists-Concert Management, 1989 Sept. 22 (Box-folder 43/93)
    - Columbia University in the City of New York see: Lang, Paul see: Lockwood, Normand and Vona see: Luening, Otto see: Moore, Douglas
    - Columbia University Press, 1966 May 23 (Box-folder 43/94)
    - Columbia University Teachers College, 1938, 1948 (Box-folder 43/95)
    - Command Records, 1964 July 10 (Box-folder 43/96)
    - Commentary, 1966 Aug 18 (Box-folder 43/97)
    - Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1964 Feb. 12 (Box-folder 43/98)
    - Community Concert Service, 1947 (Box-folder 43/99)
    - Composers Publishing Club, 1939 (Box-folder 44/1)
    - Composers Recordings, Inc., 1964-65 (Box-folder 44/2)
    - Concord Summer School of Music, 1938 Jun. 22 (Box-folder 44/3)
    - Concordia Publishing House, 1966 (Box-folder 44/4)
    - Congregation Emanu-El, 1951, 1976 (Box-folder 44/5)
    - Connecticut College, 1942 (Box-folder 44/6)
    - Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc., 1943 Aug. 30 (Box-folder 44/7)
    - Converse College, 1938-1948, 1964-1966, 1975, undated, Folders: 44/8 1938-1939 44/9 1940-48, 1964-66, 1975 44/10 Undated (Box-folder 44/8-10)
    - Coolidge, Elizabeth Sprague, 1938 Sept. 29 (Box-folder 44/11)
    - Corbató, Emily, 1965-86 (Box-folder 44/12)
    - Cornell University Libraries, 1974 Feb. 22 (Box-folder 44/13)
    - Cowell, Henry, 1953, 1983 and Sidney Cowell (Box-folder 44/14)
    - Cricket: magazine for children, 1974 Sept. 24 (Box-folder 44/15)
    - Curtin, Phyllis, n.d. (Box-folder 44/16)
    - The Curtis Institute of Music, 1939, 1941 (Box-folder 44/17)
    - "C" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 44/18)
    - Daedalus, 1964 June 9 (Box-folder 44/19)
    - Daily Express, 1954 July 21 (Box-folder 44/20)
    - Daily News/Evening News see: Ussher, Bruno
    - Dartmouth College see: Leich, Roland
    - Davies, Mrs. Ralph (Louise), 1980 June 30, n.d. (Box-folder 44/21)
    - Denison University, 1967 Jan. 9 (Box-folder 44/22)
    - Department of Rehabilitation, 1989 Dec. 19 (Box-folder 44/23)
    - Detroit Symphony Orchestra, 1932 May 23 (Box-folder 44/24)
    - Deutsche Medizinische Gesellschaft, 1916 Mar. 17 (Box-folder 44/25)
    - Diablo: the magazine of the East Bay, 1989 (Box-folder 44/26)
    - Dodd, Mead & Company, 1965 Feb. 3 (Box-folder 44/27)
    - Down beat, 1965 Apr. 13 (Box-folder 44/28)
    - Downes, Olin, 1944 Sept. 8 see also: The New York Times (Box-folder 44/29)
    - Drinker Biddle & Reath, 1945 June 28 (Box-folder 44/30)
    - Duke University Library, 1974 Mar. 14 (Box-folder 44/31)
    - "D" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 44/32)
    - East Bay Regional Park District, 1977 Aug. 29 (Box-folder 44/33)
    - Eastman School of Music see: The University of Rochester
    - Edward B. Marks Music Corporation, 1966 July 6 (Box-folder 44/34)
    - Elkan-Vogel, Inc., 1972 June 30 (Box-folder 44/35)
    - Elkus, John, 1944, 1962-65, 1974-79 and Elizabeth Elkus (Box-folder 44/36)
    - Elmcrest Manor, 1964 (Box-folder 44/37)
    - Eloesser, Leo, 1932-67, n.d. (Box-folder 44/38)
    - Elwell, Herbert, 1960 (Box-folder 44/39)
    - Emory University, 1968 Mar. 22 (Box-folder 44/40)
    - Erskine, Dorothy, 1930-42, 1957-60, 1974, n.d. (Box-folder 44/41)
    - Erskine, John, 1941-43, 1974 (Box-folder 44/42)
    - Erskine, Morse, 1936, 1954 (Box-folder 45/1)
    - Esquire, n.d. (Box-folder 45/2)
    - The Etude music magazine, 1943 June 16 (Box-folder 45/3)
    - "E" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 45/4)
    - Fairbank, Janet, n.d. (Box-folder 45/5)
    - The family, 1932, 1951 (Box-folder 45/6)
    - Farrar, Straus & Giroux Inc., 1967 Oct 27 (Box-folder 45/7)
    - Field, Sara Bard, 1931, 1937-49, n.d. (Box-folder 45/8)
    - First Presbyterian Church, 1946, 1958, 1961 (Box-folder 45/9)
    - Fletcher, Stanley, 1973-79 (Box-folder 45/10)
    - The Florida State University, 1962 Dec. 12 (Box-folder 45/11)
    - Floyd, Carlisle, 1966 Mar. 6 (Box-folder 45/12)
    - Foldes, Andor, 1946-47, 1963 (Box-folder 45/13)
    - Foothill College, 1964 Mar. 16 (Box-folder 45/14)
    - The Ford Foundation, 1953-71 (Box-folder 45/15)
    - The Foundation for Environmental Design, 1966 Mar. 14 (Box-folder 45/16)
    - The Free Library of Philadelphia, 1939, 1974, 1987 (Box-folder 45/17)
    - Fresno Philharmonic Association, 1966 Mar. 9 (Box-folder 45/18)
    - Fuchs, Peter Paul see: Louisiana State University
    - Funk & Wagnalls Company, Inc., 1965 Apr. 8 (Box-folder 45/19)
    - Furman University, 1939, n.d. (Box-folder 45/20)
    - "F" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 45/21)
    - G. Schirmer, Inc., 1931, 1971, n.d. see also: Reese, Gustave (Box-folder 45/22)
    - Galaxy Music Corporation, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 45/23)
    - Gates, Fanny C., 1925-31 (Box-folder 45/24)
    - Gauthier, Eva, 1948, n.d. (Box-folder 45/25)
    - George Peabody College for Teachers, 1967 Jan. 16 (Box-folder 45/26)
    - George Mason University, 1985 July 31 (Box-folder 45/27)
    - Gish, Mrs. Herbert (Emily) see: Corbató, Emily
    - Glen Farm, n.d. (Box-folder 45/28)
    - Glenn, Carroll, 1945, n.d. (Box-folder 45/29)
    - Goldovsky Opera Institute Incorporated, 1976 Feb. 17 (Box-folder 45/30)
    - Goldsboro News-Argus, 1946 Aug. 26 (Box-folder 45/31)
    - Goldman, Maurice, n.d. (Box-folder 45/32)
    - Goldman, Richard Franko see: Peabody Institute
    - Golschmann, Vladimir, 1939 Oct. 1 (Box-folder 45/33)
    - Goossens, Boonie, 1926 Jan. 22, n.d. (Box-folder 45/34)
    - Goossens, Eugene see: Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra
    - Graham, Stuart, 1944, n.d. (Box-folder 45/35)
    - Gray, Maxine Cushing, 1936-48, 1976, 1987 (Box-folder 45/36)
    - The Great Southwest Books, 1984-85 (Box-folder 45/37)
    - Greissle, Felix see: Edward B. Marks Music Corporation
    - Grinnell College, 1947-48 (Box-folder 45/38)
    - Grunewald, Carl F., 1915-16, n.d. (Box-folder 45/39)
    - Gunn, Glen Dillard, 1940-48 see also: Bureau of Fine Arts (Box-folder 45/40)
    - "G" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 45/41)
    - Hamilton College, 1938-40, n.d. (Box-folder 45/42)
    - Hanson, Howard see: National Association of Schools of Music see: The University of Rochester
    - Harper & Brothers Publishers, 1939, 1948 (Box-folder 45/43)
    - Harper & Row, Publishers, Inc., 1971 June 24 (Box-folder 45/44)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1965, n.d. (Box-folder 45/45)
    - Harris, Johana, 1961, 1980, 1986-89 (Box-folder 45/46)
    - Harrison, Guy Fraser, 1946, 1955, 1966-68, n.d. (Box-folder 45/47)
    - Harrison, Lou, 1987 Oct. 23 (Box-folder 45/48)
    - Harvard University, 1925, 1938-48, 1966-74 (Box-folder 45/49)
    - Headley, George L., 1939 (Box-folder 45/50)
    - Heafner, Carolyn, 1981 (Box-folder 45/51)
    - Heinsheimer, Hans W., n.d. (Box-folder 45/52)
    - Henry Hadley Foundation, Inc., 1939 (Box-folder 45/53)
    - Hewitt, Helen M., 1949 (Box-folder 45/54)
    - Hi Fi/Stereo Review, n.d. (Box-folder 45/55)
    - High Fidelity, 1966 Aug. 4 (Box-folder 45/56)
    - Hines, Duncan, 1938 Jan. 15 (Box-folder 45/57)
    - Hinrichsen, Evelyn, 1978 (Box-folder 45/58)
    - Holm, Jeff, 1970, 1986-87 (Box-folder 45/59)
    - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., 1965 Jan. 18 (Box-folder 45/60)
    - Horgan, Paul, 1932-33, 1941-70, 1978-82, n.d. (Box-folder 45/61)
    - Horizon, 1962-69 (Box-folder 45/62)
    - Houston, George, 1926, n.d. (Box-folder 45/63)
    - Huntington Hartford Foundation, 1956-63 (Box-folder 45/64)
    - Hurd, Henrietta Wyeth, 1950 Aug. 31, n.d. (Box-folder 45/65)
    - Hurd, Peter, [1953]-62, n.d. (Box-folder 45/66)
    - Hutchins, Guy, 1942, 1984-88, n.d. (Box-folder 45/67)
    - "H" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 45/68)
    - The Independent, 1976 May 21 see also: Berkeley Daily Gazette (Box-folder 46/1)
    - Indiana University, 1938, 1965-66, 1980 (Box-folder 46/2)
    - Ingles, Mrs. William Constance F., 1955, 1961-86, n.d. (Box-folder 46/3)
    - International Alliance Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Pictures Machine Operators, 1938 Sept. 26 (Box-folder 46/4)
    - International Institute of Music, 1961 (Box-folder 46/5)
    - Ives, Ruth Livingston, 1946-74, n.d. (Box-folder 46/6)
    - J. Fischer & Bro., 1933 Apr. 24 (Box-folder 46/7)
    - Jahoda, Fritz, 1939 Oct. 13 (Box-folder 46/8)
    - Jalowetz, Heinrich see: Black Mountain College
    - James, Philip, 1948-53 (Box-folder 46/9)
    - Johansen, Gunnar, 1945, 1980-83, n.d. (Box-folder 46/10)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1939-41, 1964 (Box-folder 46/11)
    - Johnson, Thor, 1944, 1962 (Box-folder 46/12)
    - Juilliard School of Music, 1958, 1970 (Box-folder 46/13)
    - "J" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 46/14)
    - KQED, 1985-86 (Box-folder 46/15)
    - The Katherine Branson School, 1940 Jan. 10 (Box-folder 46/16)
    - Kaun, Bernhard, 1966, n.d. (Box-folder 46/17)
    - The John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, Friedheim Awards, 1984 (Box-folder 46/18)
    - The Kenyon Review, n.d. (Box-folder 46/19)
    - Knoblauch-Franc, Marion, 1982-83 (Box-folder 46/20)
    - Kohn, Hans, 1963-67 (Box-folder 46/21)
    - Kolisch, Rudolf, 1953 (Box-folder 46/22)
    - Komroff, Manuel, 1948-58, 1966-74, 1986, n.d. and Odette Komroff (Box-folder 46/23)
    - Korn, Peter, 1962 (Box-folder 46/24)
    - Krenek, Ernst, 1942 Jan. 14 (Box-folder 46/25)
    - "K" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 46/26)
    - Lamont School of Music see: University of Denver
    - Lang, Paul Henry, 1950, n.d. see also: The Musical Quarterly (Box-folder 46/27)
    - Langner, Lawrence, 1946-55 (Box-folder 46/28)
    - Lawson-Gould Music Publishers, Inc, 1973 Oct. 31 (Box-folder 46/29)
    - Lee, Russel van Arsdale, 1956, 1973-74, n.d. and Dorothy Lee (Box-folder 46/30)
    - Lehigh University, 1966 May 16 (Box-folder 46/31)
    - Lehmann, Lotte, 1968 Sept. 20 (Box-folder 46/32)
    - Leich, Roland, 1941, n.d. (Box-folder 46/33)
    - Lengyel, Cornel, 1959, 1967 and Teresa Lengyel (Box-folder 46/34)
    - Leonardo Academy of Arts and Science see: Johansen, Gunnar
    - Lert, Richard, n.d. (Box-folder 46/35)
    - Leschui, Joana, n.d. (Box-folder 46/36)
    - The Librarian of Mills College, 1974 Feb. 11 see also: Mills College (Box-folder 46/37)
    - Library and Museum of the Performing Arts see: The New York Public Library
    - The Library of Congress, 1964, 1974-84, 1989 (Box-folder 46/38)
    - Liebling-Wood, Inc., 1938-39 (Box-folder 46/39)
    - Limestone College, 1967 Jan. 16 (Box-folder 46/40)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc., 1962 June 13 (Box-folder 46/41)
    - Lincoln Southeast High School, 1977 Apr. 21 (Box-folder 46/42)
    - Little, Brown and Company, 1932, 1966, 1978 (Box-folder 46/43)
    - Lockwood, Normand, 1948-78, n.d. and Vona Lockwood (Box-folder 46/44)
    - Loesser, Arthur, 1941, n.d. (Box-folder 46/45)
    - Lomax, Alan, 1945 Dec. 4 (Box-folder 46/46)
    - Lombard, Eugene, 1925-37, n.d. and Juliette Lombard (Box-folder 46/47)
    - Longy School of Music, 1957 Jan. 15, n.d. (Box-folder 46/48)
    - Louisiana State University, 1957, 1966-67 (Box-folder 46/49)
    - Luening, Otto, 1925-87, n.d.; Ethel Luening, and Catherine Luening (Box-folder 46/50)
    - "L" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 46/51)
    - MacDowell Colony, 1948, 1955 (Box-folder 47/1)
    - MacDowell, Mrs. Edward, 1936-37, 1948-55 (Box-folder 47/2)
    - Mandychewski, Vicki, 1914, 1922-1932, n.d., Folders: 47/3 1914, 1922-24 47/4 1925-32, n.d. (Box-folder 47/3-4)
    - Manhattan School of Music, 1966, 1971 (Box-folder 47/5)
    - Manorhouse, 1961 June 16 (Box-folder 47/6)
    - Martin, Albert, 1947 (Box-folder 47/7)
    - Mars Hill College, 1961 May 16 (Box-folder 47/8)
    - Marshall, Albert, 1932, 1941, 1957-61, n.d. (Box-folder 47/9)
    - Marvin, Frederick, 1986-89 (Box-folder 47/10)
    - Mason, Daniel Gregory, 1940 Sept. 14 (Box-folder 47/11)
    - Massachusetts State College, 1948 (Box-folder 47/12)
    - Mazzeo, Rosario, 1971 Jan. 30 (Box-folder 47/13)
    - McClosky, David Blair, 1952, 1977-78 (Box-folder 47/14)
    - Meet The Composer Inc., 1989 Apr. 13 (Box-folder 47/15)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association, 1947 Feb. 26 (Box-folder 47/16)
    - Meyer, Harry G., n.d. (Box-folder 47/17)
    - Mills College, 1939, 1958 see also: The Librarian of Mills College (Box-folder 47/18)
    - Milton Academy, 1943 June 15 (Box-folder 47/19)
    - Minneapolis Symphony Orchestra, 1945, 1950 (Box-folder 47/20)
    - Minnesota Public Radio, 1987 Nov. 19 (Box-folder 47/21)
    - Minnesota Railroads, 1958 Apr. 16 (Box-folder 47/22)
    - Moore, Douglas, 1937-68, n.d. (Box-folder 47/23)
    - Mitropoulos, Dimitri see: Minneapolis Symphony Orchestra
    - Mount Union College, 1976 Apr. 30 (Box-folder 47/24)
    - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1966 Jan. 18 (Box-folder 47/25)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1939 Dec. 13 (Box-folder 47/26)
    - Music Associates of Aspen, 1986 Nov. 14 (Box-folder 47/27)
    - Music at Kohl Mansion, 1985, n.d. (Box-folder 47/28)
    - Music Journal, 1963, 1977 (Box-folder 47/29)
    - Music Library Association, 1960 Dec. 31 (Box-folder 47/30)
    - Music Press Inc., 1946-48 (Box-folder 47/31)
    - Music Publishers Holding Corporation, 1948 Mar. 18 (Box-folder 47/32)
    - The Music Teachers' Association of California, 1976 Mar. 8 (Box-folder 47/33)
    - Musical America, 1948, 1965 (Box-folder 47/34)
    - Musical Courier, 1937 July 19 (Box-folder 47/35)
    - The Musical Quarterly, 1964, 1979 see also: Reese, Gustave see also: Writings series, Prose subseries, [Our Musical Idiom] (Box-folder 47/36)
    - Musikwissenschaftliches Institut, 1963 Sept. 27 (Box-folder 47/37)
    - Myers, Margaret, 1959-64, n.d. (Box-folder 47/38)
    - "M" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 47/39)
    - N.A.A.N.A.C.M., 1961 Feb. 24 (Box-folder 47/40)
    - NBC, Inc., 1939 (Box-folder 47/41)
    - The Nation, 1961-66 (Box-folder 47/42)
    - National Association for American Composers and Conductors, 1940, 1945 (Box-folder 47/43)
    - National Association of Schools of Music, 1942-47 (Box-folder 47/44)
    - National Association of Teachers of Singing, Inc., 1974 June 1 (Box-folder 47/45)
    - National Concert and Artist Corporation, 1945 Jun. 12 (Box-folder 47/46)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1966-77 (Box-folder 47/47)
    - National Federation of Music Clubs, 1939, 1945, n.d. (Box-folder 47/48)
    - National Geographic Society, 1988 May 4 (Box-folder 47/49)
    - The National Institute of Arts and Letters, 1962 Feb. 21 (Box-folder 47/50)
    - National Institute of Music and Theater, 1989 Feb. 24 (Box-folder 47/51)
    - National Symphony Orchestra, 1941 May 23 (Box-folder 47/52)
    - The New England Conservatory, 1937-39, 1979 (Box-folder 47/53)
    - New Mexico Music Festival at Taos, 1975-84, n.d. (Box-folder 47/54)
    - New Republic, 1954, 1964 see also: The Atlantic Monthly (Box-folder 47/55)
    - New York, Executive Chamber, 1987-88 (Box-folder 47/56)
    - New York Federation of Music Clubs, Inc., 1948 (Box-folder 47/57)
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1953 Feb. 24, n.d. (Box-folder 47/58)
    - New York Philharmonic, 1965, 1972 see also: Writings series, Prose subseries, Articles (Box-folder 47/59)
    - The New York Public Library, 1974 (Box-folder 47/60)
    - The New York Review of Books, 1973 Oct. 24 (Box-folder 47/61)
    - New York Shakespeare Festival, 1976 (Box-folder 47/62)
    - The New York Times, 1940-46, 1955, 1966 see also: Chasins, Abram (Box-folder 47/63)
    - New York University, 1962, 1965 (Box-folder 47/64)
    - New York University Press see: New York University
    - The New Yorker1987, n.d. (Box-folder 47/65)
    - Newhall, Nancy, 1952, 1962-66 (Box-folder 47/66)
    - Nies-Berger, Edouard, 1948-53 (Box-folder 48/1)
    - Nixon, Marni, 1974-79 (Box-folder 48/2)
    - Nordoff, Paul, 1971-72, n.d. (Box-folder 48/3)
    - North Point Press, 1987-89 (Box-folder 48/4)
    - Northwestern University, 1916-17, 1941-48, 1974, n.d. (Box-folder 48/5)
    - Norview High School, 1954 Nov. 29 (Box-folder 48/6)
    - Nowak, Lionel, 1932, 1946-53, 1964, 1974, 1981-91, n.d. (Box-folder 48/7)
    - "N" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 48/8)
    - [Oakland, Office of the Mayor], 1986 Oct. 16 (Box-folder 48/9)
    - Oakland Symphony Orchestra, 1984-85 (Box-folder 48/10)
    - Oakland Tribune, 1964 Mar. 5 (Box-folder 48/11)
    - Oberlin College, 1966, 1974, 1986 (Box-folder 48/12)
    - Occidental College, 1964 Apr. 27 (Box-folder 48/13)
    - Office of the Assessor, 1939 May 18 see also: Miscellaneous series, Financial/legal (Box-folder 48/14)
    - Ohio University, 1966 Dec. 29 (Box-folder 48/15)
    - The Oklahoma City Symphony Society see: Harrison, Guy Fraser
    - Old First Concerts, 1974 Oct. 24 (Box-folder 48/16)
    - The Open Court Publishing Company, 1911, 1913 (Box-folder 48/17)
    - The Orchestra School, 1939 Oct. 27 (Box-folder 48/18)
    - Ossabaw Island Project, n.d. (Box-folder 48/19)
    - Oxford University Press, Inc., 1964, 1971 (Box-folder 48/20)
    - "O" Miscellaneous (Box-folder 48/21)
    - Pantheon Books, 1967 June 5 (Box-folder 48/22)
    - Parker, William, n.d. (Box-folder 48/23)
    - Pattison, Lee, 1937-45, 1958 (Box-folder 48/24)